<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="truths">
        <item>"Would you swallow or spit"</item>
        <item>"Your lover has been magically transformed into an animal, and the only way to restore your lover is to mate with them. Here's the question: Which animal would cause you the least psychological damage?"</item>
        <item>"If you could be born again would choose to be a different sex to what you are? Why?"</item>
        <item>"Who is the second most attractive person here"</item>
        <item>"Who in this group  would you marry, fuck and kill"</item>
        <item>" Would you rather fuck a goat and have nobody ever find out, or not have to fuck a goat but have everyone think that you did."</item>
        <item>" Have you ever had sexual thoughts or dreams about anyone in the room."</item>
        <item>"Your plane crashes on an island, and only you and the girls here survive. You must choose one to FUCK (and you can only fuck her), one to TALK to you (and go hunt food with you), and one to stay in the tent you built to COOK. "</item>
        <item>"Who do you think in the group has the smallest and largest penis"</item>
        <item>"What's the nicest thing anyone has ever done for you?"</item>
        <item>"What moment of your life were you most truly happy?"</item>
        <item>"Would you rather sit on a dick and eat cake or sit on a cake and eat dick"</item>
        <item>"Who in this room would you be most embarrassed to introduce to your parents?"</item>
        <item>"How many people in this room would you date"</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="dares">
        <item>"Do your best impression of a baby being born."</item>
        <item>"Rate everyone here 1-10 in terms of personality."</item>
        <item>"Curse as badly as you can for 20 seconds."</item>
        <item>"Pretend to date someone for a day."</item>
        <item>"Name one thing you would change about each person here."</item>
        <item>"Show everyone here your youtube history"</item>
        <item>"Exchange a clothing item with the player of opposite gender. (Jackets don't count)"</item>
        <item>"Give a person in this group a foot massage"</item>
        <item>"Let the group pose you in an embarrassing position and take a picture."</item>
        <item>"Text to your bff 'I kinda have a crush on you wanna go out?' And don't reply to any of their messages."</item>
        <item>"Go up to someone and reciet a copy paste that is choosen by the group "</item>
        <item>"Put you head on the lap of the person to your right for a minute"</item>
        <item>"Touch noses with another person (picked by asker) for 60 seconds straight. No closing eyes."</item>
        <item>"Unzip someone of the opposite sex's pants with their teeth"</item>
        <item>"For the rest of the night, you must no longer speak using any form of the verb “to be.” So: is, am, was, were, are… among others, no longer in your vocabulary. Including contractions (you can’t say “I’m” since it’s just “I am”"</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>